What's up?
What's going on, eh?
I apologize if I sound a little nasal.
I'm not entirely over the sickness, but I'm totally healthy, you know?
It's just my nose, so... I may have to excuse myself a couple times.
Yes, I feel better, Sturmuler, thanks.
I am doing well.
I feel like an animal.
Good one.
Congrats on very, very nearly 100k subs.
Thank you.
I still can't believe it.
That we're that close.
Get some medicine from the medicine.
Man, that's the last medicine I need.
Get away from me with that.
No.
I was expecting a 6-7 day break.
Me too!
But I kind of got over it quick.
I hope it's not a temporary thing.
I hope I'm actually fine now, and I'm not gonna do shit again tomorrow.
We'll see.
Hello, potion seller.
I'm going into well, and I need your strongest potions.
I see you know your references well.
Animal well.
What's going on?
You can't handle my well, traveller.
Uh, hey, Mr. Hugo.
You plan to play cookie clicker or idle slayer at some point?
What is that?
It would be great to see you in a clicker or idle game.
What?
Is it one of those games where you just click?
Because if that's the case, then the answer is no.
That sounds terrible.
I mean, okay, I can't knock it because I haven't tried it, but...
Boy, can I prematurely judge it.
Music name?
Uh, I don't know.
But it's from Ark Raiders.
Guys, Ark Raiders?
I started it yesterday.
I've been watching some gameplay from it and some trailers throughout the time I was sick and stuff.
And I was already sold there, you know?
I was convinced this game was good.
Uh, so my plan was to play it off-stream.
You know, I always have some game that I play off-stream.
You know, like StarCraft or World of Warcraft or...
Battlefield or, in this case, Ark Raiders.
But I thought, you know what?
Let me actually record it for once.
And maybe I'll make a series out of it, you know?
Call it Off The Record or something.
Where I stream games I wouldn't normally stream.
Which sounds ridiculous.
But I gotta tell you...
Ark Raiders...
From the short time I've played it...
I'm like three or four hours into it at this point.
I think.
That game...
Is a fucking...
Masterpiece.
I have no words.
It is the best online game I have played in 13 years.
It is unbelievable.
These developers deserve all the praise in the world.
I cannot state how good of a game that is.
It's magical.
It's truly magical.
You've gotta play it.
There.
I said it.
Haha.
It's what Marathon should have been.
I don't know what that is.
All I know is that game was made for me.
What was it called?
Ark Raiders.
By Embark Studios.
It's former Battlefield developers...
Quite high up in the dice chain...
That decided to make their own company and make a new game.
I don't have an affiliate link.
I wish I was sponsored by them.
In fact, I haven't been sponsored by anyone yet.
I've gotten a lot of offers, but...
I don't wanna just play random games...
That I don't wanna play, you know?
But if, someday...
There's a game that I'm planning on playing, and there's a sponsor saying, Hey, we wanna pay you for playing our game...
Then obviously I'm gonna do it, but...
That hasn't happened yet.
Raid Shadow Legends.
Yeah, that's coming up, guys.
Who knows?
Maybe it's a good game.
I just...
Don't wanna play it.
I have a feeling it's not a good game, but...
Who knows?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Uh...
Those are...
No, I don't wanna know.
Thank you.
Was painful?
It sucks, dude.
From my perspective.
People are free to think differently.
War Thunder.
I actually did play War Thunder back in the day when it was good.
I remember, and maybe it's still a thing.
But I remember a time when War Thunder was about...
Dogfighting.
There were no tanks.
That didn't even exist.
And there was such a thing as...
Real full-time battles.
Where the UI was reduced.
Realism was, you know, increased.
It was still a bit arcadey.
But those days were golden days.
That was so much fun.
It was the truly...
Mainstream, sort of realistic flying simulator.
Where you could play against other people at the time.
And it wasn't too over-the-top realistic, you know?
Too bad...
It died, man.
It's not a thing anymore, I don't think.
Dingleberry, what's up?
I just finished your entire Blind Minecraft playthrough.
And it was the best YouTube series I've ever seen?
Damn.
This is the first stream I've ever caught you live.
Okay, but know that this is day five of Animal Well.
So there's gonna be some spoilers, I guess, if you haven't played the game.
Thank you for saying that, though.
I've heard that a lot.
People really enjoy the first season of Minecraft.
It's quite popular nowadays.
Now it's all about leaking military secrets?
I've heard about that!
What is going on?
Why is that a thing?
Will there be more wrap-up streams?
Yeah, one more.
I'm just waiting for the community thingy to be done.
They're making an adventure map.
And it's not quite done yet, as far as I understand.
So when that's done, I'm gonna play it.
And, yeah.
When should we expect Minecraft Season 3?
I don't know, when I feel like playing again.
And I can't give you a time on that.
I've just been playing so much Minecraft, it's time for something else for a while.
But who knows?
It could be soon.
Could be in a long while.
I really don't know.
Posting secret classified documents in the Discord for the homies.
But why are people doing...
Why is that a thing there?
It's so weird.
Next stream game?
I don't know, actually.
I decided to...
Well, I wanted to stream Amnesia, but then I decided, you know what?
It's probably better for an offline game.
So maybe I'll actually not do a horror game next?
Or stream?
I haven't decided.
I'm gonna think about it.
What's this music?
It's from Ark Raiders.
I don't know what the track is called, but it's from a masterpiece called Ark Raiders.
Yes.
Yeah, maybe Little Nightmares.
Oh, that's a horror game, right?
Maybe it's not too horror-y.
I wanted to stream Amnesia, but I forgot!
Nice.
Very good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm still planning a short game.
It could be Iron Long, actually.
I've heard it's very short, so...
Could be a good one to throw in there, you know?
Is Ark player single player?
No, it is an online game.
It is a PvE PvP game.
Or a PvE-VP.
It's an extraction shooter.
And take it from me, okay?
If you didn't like Tarkov, you're the same as me.
I hated Tarkov.
This is nothing like Tarkov.
Thank God.
This game actually is good.
It's not too complicated.
It's sleek, it's polished, it's fucking visually stunning.
From an audio perspective, they nailed it.
I've never heard anything like it.
The game is...
unbelievable.
Yeah, there.
I think I've sung the praises enough.
You would think I'm sponsored by them, but I'm not.
Then again, I only played a little bit of Tarkov.
I got so overwhelmed by it.
I just didn't...
It wasn't for me, basically.
There is a list of games people have suggested.
It's pretty much my backlog.
You can check it out on Backlogged.
There's a link to it on the Discord.
I put all the games there that I want to play.
That's on the list.
Plans for Animal Well?
Where are we gonna be?
Let me see.
We're gonna be animaling and...
Welling.
I don't know.
We're gonna figure it out.
Yeah.
You could go old school and play Stronghold or Age of Empires.
You know, I really want to play Stronghold again.
There's also an HD remaster of it, so it totally works on modern hardware.
Would be a good one.
Love the music in that game, too.
Watching Subnautica.
I can't wait for Subnautica 2.
I hope it's as good as the first when it comes out.
I don't think I'll ever stream Tetris.
I just don't think it's that much fun.
I mean, I think I've played it a little bit, but it's just rotating the fucking...
Tetris pieces.
It's not for me, I don't think.
I don't have the reaction times and brain power to actually play that game.
Denmark has been having lots of rain, yeah.
It's been quite grey and rainy lately.
But that's good!
It's better for gaming.
No glare in the monitor.
It's perfect.
What do you think about Subnautica versus Below Zero?
I think they're both excellent games.
I think I like the first one a bit more, but the second one was excellent.
Especially the music.
Water stream when?
I don't know what that means.
Is there a game called Water?
Speaking of Water, you know what?
I'm gonna try and hydrate more today.
More than usual.
Alright.
Let's play some Animal Well.
Let's fucking do it.
Oh, that is the smoothest transition you've ever heard.
I know it is.
Okay.
Here we go.
Look at that.
Animal Well.
Now.
What the hell was I doing?
Let's figure it out.
Oh yeah, I was chilling at home.
Oh, I remember.
I was...
Oh, I also need to remember all the keybinds here.
We're good.
Right, this mofo right here.
I was trying to wait for a full hour.
And, yeah.
Basically, clocks are my, uh...
Or clocks are my arch nemesis.
Arch nemesis.
Ssssss.
You know what I mean.
I don't do well with clocks, as you all know.
Um...
I guess the plan now...
Is to just keep exploring.
I mean, there's still things we haven't done.
I wanna try and get to this chest.
And all the other chests I have marked on the map.
Because I have marked quite a few.
Uh...
We also gotta find...
More candles.
For this stuff here.
So, I guess we're just gonna be walking around a bit.
Also...
I wanna rescue more of the animals over here.
Yeah.
So, we gotta find, uh...
More arrows.
Basically.
The thing is, I don't know...
Where I should go first.
What is this?
Needs EC.
I have no idea what that means.
Electrified, uh...
Christ.
That needs a key, but this is useless.
Oh yeah, wait.
We have a key, no?
Yeah, we have a key.
We have a key.
Uh, so there's gotta be a door somewhere that we can open with it.
Not that door up there.
Cause that's gonna be...
Useless.
I also put some question marks.
Oh yeah, there was a chest in this region over here.
That we can't get to.
I think I may need another item, I'm not sure.
But, uh, there's spikes and shit, and we can't really do anything about it.
There's also a slot here.
For something.
Oh yeah!
Uh, I think we need to find a, um...
Whatchamacallit.
Like a hamster...
Wheel.
A hamster wheel.
Because that fits in the slot.
So that we can, uh...
Utilize some kind of mechanism, basically.
Yeah.
Was there anything else I needed to do at home here?
Oh yeah, we have this door, but we can't open it with our current key for some reason.
So I'm guessing we need another key.
Or some other way to get in there.
Why did I mark this with a triangle and no...
Line.
What's happening?
What is this?
What's going on there?
So, I think...
A smart way to do this is to just keep exploring areas where I think there is something we haven't found.
Like here.
Or here.
Because getting to unexplored places is probably the wisest thing we can do.
At the moment.
Just to find...
Oh, more eggs as well.
We gotta find more eggs.
For sure.
Yeah.
So, in other words, we have a lot to do.
But I suspect we're gonna be running around quite a bit with no success for a while.
Just because the map is so large and I don't know where to start, you know?
But we do have the remote.
So we can, uh...
Beepity boop things and see things appear.
Which I enjoy.
Speaking of the remote.
Beep, beep, beep.
Nice.
Uh...
Get me up here.
So, this was also...
Yeah, this spot here...
I think that these skulls somehow hold a secret.
Maybe their orientation.
Maybe the number of skulls in these piles can correspond to a numerical value.
And if we have numerical values in a sequence, we have a song.
Right?
Uh, let me see.
Yeah, like this, right?
So this is one.
This is two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Okay.
That's basically the idea right now.
Ah, but how would I get in there?
I suspect it's gonna be via a song.
But I could be wrong.
Let me go hit the gong.
I had to rhyme there, okay?
I have a need to rhyme.
At times.
It's inexplicable.
Jump!
That does that.
Oh, also, I gotta check every screen we go to.
For arrows.
You know what?
Let's try and go do that first.
Um...
You know what?
I'm gonna mark something here.
On this map.
So the arrows we found were over here.
Right here.
This, uh, spot here.
This spot here.
Notice how close they are together, but then again.
Didn't we also find arrows somewhere in this region?
So maybe it's not all localized...
There.
Yeah, we gotta explore this entire place.
From top to bottom.
Once more.
Just give it another look, you know?
Because there are animals...
To rescue.
So to get here, the best way...
I think is...
Oh my god.
Do we really not have...
Oh, L.
L was...
That one.
I forgot what that was short for.
Let me play a song.
For you guys.
I know you like music.
Yeah.
I wish that sound...
Was played in other places in the game.
Oh, I know.
Leper.
That's what the L was for.
Okay, so I'm in this region now.
Let me go save the game here, so that if I die, I come back here.
Let's play it safe and smart.
Also, there was a wallaby here at some point.
And now it's gone.
Like, what's up with that?
Something's going on there.
Also, we have this.
Let's not forget.
I kind of forgot that.
Oh yeah, and look for breakable floors.
That's another thing.
Breakable floors.
Ring up the people.
Let them know what we're up to.
Otherwise, they're going to be worried sick about us.
So I pretty much scoured the entire upstairs section here last time for arrows, and I didn't find any.
Now, of course, it is possible that I simply missed it.
But I'm going to start from somewhere else this time.
So those two...
Actually, I kind of want to...
Yeah, let's go down to where we found the other arrow.
I'll have to remember this entire sequence of events here.
Okay, so we can go left now.
And we had to take a shark at some point.
Also, while we're traveling, maybe have a look.
There's nothing on the wall.
Okay.
Quick, quick, quick, quick!
Where's the...
There...
Fuck!
One complaint I have.
They should have, like, separate keybindings for these things instead of having to scroll through them.
It's really annoying having to do that in the middle of action, you know?
Sock the ball.
I mean...
Haha!
Sock the, uh, you know...
The...
You know what I mean.
The bubble.
I couldn't find the right word.
Okay, so here...
You need to be freed right there.
I'm going to call you...
Sphincter.
Wait, what is that?
What is a sphincter?
Isn't that a body part?
I'm not sure.
Or is that, like, one of those, uh, Egyptian animals?
Isn't that an Egyptian animal?
Okay.
Smash that.
I'm a smasher today.
Smash, smash, smash.
Oh!
We got a reverse.
Also, let me just scan this.
Now that we have...
Let me also...
Okay, okay, okay.
Like, the light should really be on at all times.
Just in case we run by arrows and miss it, you know?
Damn, I have a lot of HP.
Look at that.
That's beautiful.
Let's save the game here now.
That opens that.
Okay, I remember this kinda.
Yeah.
Now everything...
This is where we got chased, remember?
I'm really scanning the walls here.
Oh, shit.
I actually just jumped normally.
What am I doing?
Yeah, we got one here that needs to be freed.
Let's mark it, actually.
So...
What should the symbol be?
Maybe, uh...
Hmm...
SOS.
Here, and then also...
I think...
Here?
Where was the other one?
I think it was here.
SOS.
Yeah.
Those were the arrows I found last time.
And they're actually kind of...
Obvious, when you look at it.
Dude, I...
I'm really enjoying the graphics in this game.
I wish more games did something like this.
This old-school style.
I wonder how good this game would look on an actual CRT.
I know the game is trying to, um...
Emulate the look of a CRT.
But if you put this on a CRT, would it all be broken?
Because, you know...
Maybe they don't mesh well?
I don't know.
It's interesting.
The question is, do I somehow continue here?
I could activate the mechanism again.
Can't I?
Actually, I don't think I can because, uh...
The thing that was moving this is now gone, right?
Maybe I'm stuck here.
There's no way I can get softlocked, though.
That would be stupid, right?
So...
Let's just assume there's nothing else to the left.
For now.
Yeah.
That seems wise.
Meow!
She sounds like a cat, doesn't it?
What?
Oh, what's this?
Why is there a little, uh, path here?
Oh, right.
Okay.
What was this down here?
Right.
This is the one I never marked where it took me.
Hmm.
There's no arrows here.
Oh, wait a minute.
There's something on the pillar.
Or not.
Light up the room.
Yeah, I don't see anything here.
Nothing.
Remind me!
Oh, shark!
Look for stuff on the way.
Oh, we're going far up.
Very far up.
Holy shit!
Whoa!
Okay.
Takes me here.
Let's mark it.
Ah, it looks like a K.
X.
There you go.
Look for arrows.
See, I may be too far away now.
No, no.
This is still sort of the same purplish region.
I'm going to assume all the arrows are in the purple region.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
That's what I did.
Look for breakable floors, too.
I think it's hard to tell.
Like, I can't really be sure if something is breakable or not.
It's really hard to tell a difference, I think.
I do remember this.
Do I even want to be here?
Hold on, I'm going to die.
Okay.
Can I, like, get back to the safe spot real quick?
Because then I'm going to be all the way downstairs, right?
This is smart.
Nice.
I mean, obviously we lost our extra hearts there, but that's fine.
Not like we need them right now.
Okay, so that leads us back up there.
Good to know.
Let me go.
Let me go back upstairs.
I don't see anything down here.
Nothing.
Yeah.
What was the stuff on the right?
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I have to somehow dislodge the hamster down below.
The wheel, I mean.
And then bring the wheel to another slot.
But how...
Maybe I can lure them with something.
And they follow me.
Is that a thing I can do?
Shit, I didn't mean to do that.
Wait, why did I instantly die?
I thought I had 4 HP.
Okay.
Back up.
Yeah, I don't see anything here.
I think I may need to reverse the direction of the spin.
If I have any need to go back, right?
Wait, what?
Oh, no, it was upstairs.
Already confused myself.
Here we go.
Okay, so now we do this.
There we go.
Get reversed, nope, also.
Oh, yeah.
What is the plan?
I want to go back up, so I have to go here.
Jump!
Nice.
Okay, so this shark takes me...
Back up to there.
Is there anything in this room?
Okay.
Take me.
Take me on a trip.
What was up here?
Oh, is that...
Is that not, uh...
Breakable?
Look.
Oh, it is!
Ahaha!
Oh, we got arrows!
Would you look at that!
Taking a picture of that.
Yike.
Instantly saw that one.
Well, I mean instantly as in, uh...
I saw the arrows instantly.
Uh, okay.
The question is, which one does that belong to?
Uh, I guess I'll find out.
Also, look above me!
There's a, uh, kangaroo!
In the back!
What is that all about?
Maybe the kangaroo is promising, uh...
Secrets or something.
So if I find kangaroo...
I don't know, I'm fucking...
Imagining things, I think.
Uh...
I need to go this way.
Wait, do I need to go that way?
No, no, it was downstairs.
But I can't get back downstairs.
Unless I get squished.
Yeah!
Smart.
Like getting squished.
Okay, um...
So we had one down here, didn't we?
Let's just go there and check that.
Knowing my luck though, it's gonna be the wrong one.
Watch.
There.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Um...
Loot.
Let me see.
So, up left, up left, down left, down left, down.
Okay.
Up left, up left, down left, down left, down.
Okay, so it's the wrong one.
Gotcha.
It's gotta be the other one then.
Just wanted to double check, you know.
Uh, here.
Here we go.
Yeah!
There we go!
You're free!
Come on!
Go!
Go, go, go!
And there it went.
Nice.
Okay, so we're missing one SOS.
Gotta look for the arrows.
Maybe there's arrows in here.
Are there any arrows...
downstairs here maybe?
I'm really looking here, you know.
I...
I can't see it.
I don't see anything.
Okay, but, uh...
This is actually good.
It's promising because now we know that...
almost certainly...
it has to be somewhere in the purple region.
But the purple region is quite big, so, you know.
Uh, what have we checked?
We've checked the downstairs.
We have checked...
here.
What is inside here again?
I forgot.
So, okay, let me actually mark this as well.
So where did we find this just now?
We found it here.
So, one, two, three.
And we also had one over...
I believe here.
Is there any pattern here with these?
Would it be... wouldn't it be fucking awesome?
Imagine.
Like, imagine this...
was a spot where you found an arrow.
This was a spot.
So it forms a circle or something, so you could sort of...
guesstimate where the others are.
You know what I mean?
That would be a cool puzzle.
Oh!
Cuckoo!
I missed it!
I missed the cuckoo!
Uh, but I guess...
Oh!
We have a...
We have a timer.
Sixteen.
So we know when...
Do I want to head back though?
Like...
Yeah, I guess I'll head back.
I mean...
Let's just try and keep an eye on it.
Okay.
Let's go...
Oh god, I don't know.
Let's go to L.
No, no, uh...
Did we check everything down?
I think we...
did.
Let's go to L.
That is the quietest...
bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup, bup...
you've ever heard.
As if it was a silent one.
Even the background now, I'm starting to think there's something going on there, you know?
So we're approaching the spots where we already found...
some arrows.
What is that right there in the...
in the brickwork?
Something's going on.
Alright, so let's just take this room by room.
We have done...
the bottom level down here.
We have kind of done this level.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second, I'm just noticing something.
This is blue, this is purple.
This is not one color.
Oh my god, can you tell?
Look!
All of these circles are in the purple.
So we should not be here.
We should be sort of in this...
I think.
Oh, this is also...
No, that's like pink-ish.
Or violet.
Uh...
So, I think we've checked this one pretty thoroughly.
Wait, if I go to the other side, is that also purple?
No, that's more like blue.
I think.
Yeah, that's definitely more blue.
So, maybe over here?
Could be something?
Let's go that way.
That is such a slight color variation.
Wow.
Imagine if the arrows were on the elevator going down, you know?
So the sequence was repeating itself, uh, cyclically.
On the elevator.
That would be a great puzzle, wouldn't it?
Actually, they are kind of moving left and right.
Is it always left, right?
Left, right.
Left.
Right.
Okay, yeah, okay.
I thought maybe it would be left, left, left, right, right, left, right, or something, you know?
And that would be a sequence for a song.
You know what?
I'm gonna head back up here, I think.
Just to make sure.
Because I actually...
Don't wanna explore areas assuming I've gotten everything.
Because I am sometimes wrong about my assumptions.
And that is a fault of mine, I admit it.
I am not seeing anything on this screen.
We gotta change direction here now.
There we go.
Ah, wait a sec.
Maybe in here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait a minute.
Oh!
I know what's happening!
The ones we rescue go here.
And once we get all of them, we get the chest.
This is the mom.
Right?
It's Mama Cat!
Dude!
I get it now.
But, uh...
We are not in the purple region anymore.
Are we?
Is that the same purple?
Bro, hold on.
Zoom out!
Uh...
I literally can't tell.
I'm gonna assume it's not.
And then...
I'm probably wrong.
Come back later.
I can't tell.
I need to have the RGB values of the pixel.
To tell.
Okay, let's see here.
Look for breakable floors, by the way.
Now that we have the, uh...
The spinning.
Okay, I don't see anything here.
Why does this wall look breakable?
Go!
Goddamn.
I'm not seeing arrows here.
Don't fuck this up now.
Smooth.
Yeah.
What is this animal right behind me?
That is a weird animal.
And I feel like something's going on with it.
Okay, I feel like this area has been thoroughly checked.
There's nothing here.
Nothing.
And this place...
I don't see anything either.
That shark was the...
Wait, what?
Right, that took me downstairs there.
Okay.
Uh...
What have I not tried?
I guess...
This area again...
This could have something.
Maybe I didn't check it thoroughly.
I'll get back down there, I think.
Uh...
So we gotta reverse this.
There we go.
Take me on a trip.
Okay.
I don't see anything here.
Like, at all.
Ah!
Come on.
Good.
I'm looking for breakable floors in particular.
Because, uh...
That breakable floor right there revealed it, right?
So maybe I missed a break...
Oh, wait a sec then.
Dude, it looks like I can go here somehow.
You know?
If I do it right, maybe I can actually traverse down there.
Wait.
Let me try something.
Quick!
Oh!
Look at that!
Holy shit!
I don't see arrows though.
I don't see arrows.
How the fuck do I get there?
God, those splashes look so good.
Why is the chest not going beepity-beep here?
That's some BS.
Oh, it is going beep-beep there.
Okay.
I wonder if that would have gone beep-beep even though I didn't reveal that little area.
Huh.
How on earth am I gonna get in...
Okay.
Here's what I think.
Remember the chest we couldn't get to?
Um...
All the way over here.
Because there were spikes.
I think we need the same kind of tech to reach this.
Because you gotta find a way to traverse a dangerous terrain without hitting that dangerous terrain.
Do you know what I mean?
Like water or spikes.
Uh...
Something like that.
Um...
Either that, or I have to somehow...
Uh...
Use an incredibly precise...
Throw...
Of the frisbee.
Which seems frickin' impossible.
Because you can't get up again.
Like how would you even...
You would have to throw a frisbee in between these two.
And then have it travel with it.
But that is not...
Possible, I don't think.
Also, how do I get back here?
I guess I don't really.
Um...
Let me try the frisbee thing.
I mean, I don't lose HP from falling in water, right?
So...
Maybe if I'm fast enough...
Oh, wait.
Oh no, it breaks off, doesn't it?
Does it?
Whoops.
Wait, what is happening?
Oh, is it hitting the water?
Nah, it doesn't work.
Hmm...
Okay, in any case, we gotta mark this chest.
Right there.
Uh, I don't see any arrow, so...
Rip on that.
Yeah.
Let's come back later.
I think I need a special tech for that.
Uh, what have I not tried?
Let's try and see if there is a way to get all the way back here again.
I feel like there's gotta be, right?
You can't just have a region be completely locked off forever now.
That feels wrong to me.
Okay.
Or this again.
Yeah, yeah, let's quickly check this with the light source.
Also, check for breakable...
Uh, floors.
Maybe it's up there in the fog, you know?
And you have to shine on it with the light...
To reveal the arrows.
Oh man, I can see that being a thing actually.
Will they not have to go through this entire weird puzzle again?
Is that really what's happening here?
I feel like I wouldn't need the light to see this because I don't usually need a light, you know?
Like, if you...
If you look hard enough, you can see it without the light.
Let's keep it as an option.
Write it down.
Uh...
Let's do...
I don't know, man.
Let's do a, uh...
One of those.
That means...
What I just said.
Surely that's not gonna bite me in the ass later.
Um...
What's up here?
Right, this place.
And down here.
Ah, save the game, I guess.
Eat that.
That takes me back up.
Slinky.
Do we need to put something on this thing?
No, I took something from here, right?
Oh, wait a minute, there's also a little...
There's actually...
There's actually a little area up there.
With vines.
But how do we do that?
That seems impossible.
Ah!
You can't do it.
How the hell do I get up there?
Re-reveal... reveal thyself.
Chest.
Or arrows.
Wait, how the hell do I get up there?
Uh...
There's vines.
They're gonna break...
My...
Disc.
Maybe I just gotta...
Oh!
Let me try and be good at this...
Shit.
Oh, actually, I think it is possible.
You just gotta...
Hey!
Oh, it's close!
If you time it correctly...
And position it correctly...
Nope.
Yeah!
Man, it's close!
I don't think this is intended though, but...
Oh, actually, hold on.
There is...
There is something I can do.
Check this out.
You see the difference between this?
And...
Uh...
This?
I go a little higher if I delay the...
Okay, it's really...
Difficult.
What if I can do that?
Oh.
Oy!
Close.
Ah!
It keeps breaking on the vines.
Man, the...
When the vines...
Uh, vines are swinging...
It's kind of impossible.
Oh!
Oy!
This doesn't feel intended.
There's gotta be some other way up there.
Jesus.
Yeah, okay.
Hmm.
What could I use?
Maybe I play a song and a ladder appears.
A secret, uh...
Entrance.
Oh, actually.
It kinda looks like I can access it from above.
Is there a...
It's right below here, no?
Yeah, it is.
I do see...
Now, actually, there's no straight holes, but...
This right here looks maybe doable.
Fuckin' hell.
There's so many areas in this game that I wanna get to, but I just can't, you know?
I don't know why I'm keep saving the game, but...
Come on.
I just gotta position myself correctly...
With the last bubble.
Oy!
When the vines are swinging...
It's kind of impossible to do.
Oh wait, I have an idea.
Uh...
I do one, and then I swing on the other, and jump on the remaining.
Wait.
Can I not go straight up with the thing?
Okay, okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Almost.
Fuck.
Come on, quick, quick.
Oy!
Okay, okay!
This is it.
Watch.
Oy!
Okay.
Oh, that's...
There's definitely a way to do this.
You gotta time it right.
Basically, I'm waiting for that elevator.
Ah, that's gonna break.
Now!
Why does it break?
It didn't hit anything.
Does it just break naturally after a certain time?
No, it doesn't.
Okay, so it's actually hitting the vine.
That's bad.
Let's see if we can get it to go right between without breaking.
Because if we can't do that, then this is hopeless.
That's gonna hit it, right?
Ah!
There it is!
That was a good one.
Oy!
Okay, we gotta make it a little higher.
That was a perfect bubble to look at it!
Look how beautiful that is!
Oh!
No, that's not perfect.
Shit!
That's not good.
Ah, my god, dude.
There we go.
No!
Hahaha!
Oy!
That break, it broke, it broke.
Peak gameplay here, guys.
This is what you've all been wanting to see.
The bubble man in action.
He does it again!
Gah!
What?!
Why did that break?
Okay, wait a minute, I can also just...
Can I somehow lift myself up while I'm standing on a bubble?
I guess I need a updraft from below.
Can I create that?
Does this reveal anything?
Maybe...
Ooh!
Wait a sec, wait a sec.
Maybe I use the disc to fly into position when the bubble is at the right height.
No, that seems way too complicated.
YAH!
Oh!
It's totally doable, dude.
Did you see how close I was?
How the...
Frick?
Oh, wait a minute.
Can I just...
Ah, but I can't keep going...
I was trying to do the Minecraft ascension, basically.
Oh!
Why did that break?
Huh?
Okay, that bubble was bad.
Okay, I gotta find a reproducible sec.
So if I stand here...
Just fucking spam the bubbles.
They're gonna...
They're gonna fall into line.
Maybe.
Uh...
There we go.
Now.
YOOOOO!
That's the way!
Go!
Oh, it's totally doable!
Okay, I figured it out.
We just gotta not suck now.
Spam the shit out of this.
Go.
Oh, come on!
Okay.
Come on, dude.
What?
I guess I just wait a little bit?
Oh!
Oh, come on!
It's so close!
This feels janky.
I feel like...
I'm sort of, uh...
Using strategies that I'm not supposed to.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, I'm accidentally skipping...
Intended progression here.
Okay, now, go!
YESSS!
Arrows!
We've got the arrows!
Look at that!
Nice!
Let's put it in!
That's what she said?
Okay, uh, while we're here...
I'm not just gonna leave, I'm gonna...
Also, what are these weird four, uh, thingies?
What's that?
Hey!
Something's going on.
Fucking nailed it.
Okay, now we gotta go to SOS.
Good start, good start.
I think I, uh, broke the level of progression here a little bit, but that's fine.
Here we go, here we go.
Um...
What was it?
Left down...
Psh, psh, psh, psh, boom.
Okay, so...
Uh, let me try and do it while I have it open.
So I can see.
Hey!
Hey, go buddy!
Oh yeah!
Now we head back to mother.
My mama's sad!
That's an aqua song.
One of my favourite aqua songs.
It's a good one.
Save the game.
Uh, where's Mama?
Mama.
I forgot where Mama is.
Where the hell?
I have no clue.
Wait, what?
Where was I?
Oh, was it on the other side?
Oh, I think it was, it was, it was.
So we gotta go, uh, we gotta go... We gotta take a Shark Express.
Eat it.
Eat the ball.
Dude, if I ever made a game, I would make all the sound effects with my mouth.
If there was a drop, I would go...
You know, every time when you're in a cavern, and there's stalactites.
Oh right, we did this.
Uh, am I in the right spot even?
Dude, I completely fucked up here.
This is not where I'm supposed to be.
Let's go to L.
That's probably the easiest thing here.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Nice.
Uh...
L time.
Loser!
Is what that stands for.
Cause look at that loser animal.
God, that animal is such a loser.
Can't believe it.
That animal is not well.
Just saying.
Uh, so we gotta try and go...
Wait a minute, why does it look like...
I think above.
We gotta go up.
Oh, I almost got squished.
The squishing was almost real.
Gotta bonk the lamps when you see them.
It's the law!
Here we are!
Oh my god.
Wait a minute.
He's making a song.
This is a song right here.
Oh, is it all the songs combined?
There's no way I had that many arrows.
Right?
Get in there.
Weesh!
Weeeel!
We got a weeeel!
Holy shit!
Okay, okay, that's huge.
Slot time.
I told you!
Now we just gotta find...
A willing giraffe.
No, a uh...
The fucking thing that goes in the hamster...
A hamster wheel!
Hamster!
Is what we need.
But where are we right now?
Why can't I see my character?
Oh yeah, we're on the left side now.
Uh...
Should I be on the left side?
I should be on the left side, because look!
There's a slot right here!
So I gotta go...
I gotta go...
Down.
How do I go down?
Without dying.
Maybe I don't.
Also...
Ha!
Oh!
Oh, what?
No way!
Oh, sick!
I thought I had to, uh...
Just slot it into the slot!
Scarlet Egg!
Wow!
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Ha ha ha!
I'm that animal!
Whoops!
Whoa!
Okay, you can't go in water.
Where am I?
What's happening?
What's my name?
Okay, I'm here.
Wheel time!
Aw, shit!
Uh...
We gotta go...
Dude, I can't see where my character is on the screen.
When you switch screens, I have trouble seeing where my character is.
Jesus Christ!
Wow, wow, wow.
Okay, now...
Uh, it's time to slot.
Dude, that is sick!
I can...
Ride the wheel!
Dude, let's ride the wheel here.
Let's go, uh, down here.
We're gonna ride so hard.
Yeah!
By the way, did I break a vertical wall just now?
I was so entranced by what was happening that I didn't even pay attention to what the fuck was going on.
I think I may have broken a vertical wall.
Which is awesome!
Anyway, we're close to a slot.
So we gotta go to L.
Let's go.
I'm gonna wheel everywhere.
Oh.
Okay.
I guess you can't wheel when you don't fit!
Whee!
Dude, I'm gonna go shit on this animal up here now.
A big ol' poop.
Uh, but with my wheel.
I'm gonna basically say my wheel is better than your wheel.
Ah, okay, fine.
I can't get up there.
Uh, I'm actually kind of excited right now.
This is huge.
Uh, let me wheel this wall.
It didn't wheel.
Okay.
Will it wheel?
I broke the mechanism!
How cool is that?
Um...
Let me see.
Wait, what is this symbol?
Why did I make that symbol?
Oh!
Oh, right, right.
We don't need that anymore.
That's gone.
Don't need that anymore.
Where am I going right now?
I'm not, uh, going the right way.
Yeah, I'm going wrong way.
Uh, we gotta, we gotta talk to the L again.
Wow, wow, wow.
Back this way.
I did a bit of a disaster the last five minutes here, but...
Bear with me, okay?
It's gonna be worth it.
We're in for a good time, I can tell.
Okay, now.
Now we're at the right spot.
Look at my wheel.
This is awesome!
Dude, I wasn't expecting to actually find something of that much value.
By doing, um, that puzzle with the arrows.
I thought it would be a little, like, like an easter egg type deal.
It felt like an easter egg, you know?
Let's go this way!
Oh, man!
It breaks everything, too!
Uh, wait, have I been here?
Where am I?
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay, okay, I see.
So we gotta go here now.
Dude, the wheel is awesome.
What else can I do with the wheel?
Wheel and deal!
Um...
Where am I?
I'm here, okay.
Slot.
Okay, I gotta go down.
I gotta go down.
Here.
This looks breakable to me!
Breakable!
No, no.
Did I...
Did I just...
Break the wall?
Look at me!
Okay.
How do I...
Oh, it's up there.
It's up there.
Uh, I need to...
That's, uh...
Food.
Bibimbap.
Bubble me.
There we go.
Now!
Check it out!
Yeah!
Yeah, dude!
Oh, that feels good!
Uh, why am I doing this?
Okay, that's the edge there.
That's edge there.
So I...
Wait, what?
So I guess here?
Shit.
Okay.
Can't go that way.
Don't fall down water!
You bastard.
Okay, so if I change item, I lose the wheel.
Gotcha.
Now...
Interesting.
What if I just go really fast?
Go!
Okay, okay, that works.
So what now?
Oh, no.
Ah!
Oh!
Dude, how the fuck...
Let me think.
Um...
Interesting.
That is...
I don't even know what to do here.
What?
Can I leave the wheel here or something while I go?
Can I remote...
Wait, wait, can I...
Somehow...
I guess I want to go to the right.
But then that would have to be...
Here.
But then I can't get through.
It's a real conundrum.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
I have an idea, I have an idea.
Oh!
That was so smart, though.
Hold on.
I think I'm...
I'm onto something.
One HP, though.
No!
I can't reapply it in mid-air!
What the hell?
Wait, uh...
Fuck, I gotta go back here now.
Ah!
Nooooo!
Okay, play the song on my people.
Fuck me, dude.
L!
L on that one.
Wheel!
Gavilan wheel!
Gavilan deal.
Uh, up again.
Frisbee!
Maybe I have reverse direction?
No, I don't reverse.
Yes, I have reverse direction.
Just because it's annoying.
There we go.
Better!
I like this much more.
Okay.
Now.
Wheel time!
This is sick, man.
The wheel is fantastic.
Now we just gotta figure out how to actually...
solve puzzles with it.
Whoop!
Downstairs.
Now we gotta break things.
Nice.
Okay.
Let's try this again.
Basically, my plan is to keep this here so that I can...
deactivate the wheel so I can fit through the tiny hole.
Activate the wheel again mid-air.
Oh, I can, though.
So why didn't it work?
Oh, it does!
Okay.
I guess I just sucked.
Um...
Ah!
Close.
What?
I... I spammed the button!
I'm pressing the button!
What do you want from me?
What the fuck?
Why didn't the wheel appear?
I was spamming the damn button!
Weird.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Let's just get the, uh...
the blaster ready.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Don't, don't.
No, no.
I don't want none of that.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, wait a minute.
I have a better idea.
Why don't we, wha...
Hello?
Why don't we just...
do that?
Hello?
Well, well, well!
I feel stupid.
Okay, now, what?
Um, we need, we need three buttons.
I see a button on the left.
Ah, damn, we gotta get to that from...
this side, huh?
Unless I can...
remote my way inside.
No...
remotation here.
Okay, so what is the deal with the wheel?
I guess I can go click a button.
Why not?
Let's just go click this button.
There.
Uh...
Oh!
That...
activates...
the fan, okay.
Activates the fan.
Ah...
Wait a sec.
Check this out.
Yeah.
Now we have to...
wheel this over.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
That's actually pretty cool.
Really neat.
Get out of the wheel.
Yeah!
That's...
That's such a good puzzle!
Love that one!
That's cool.
Uh...
Now...
we gotta click the button up there.
But that should be easy enough.
Just do this.
Also, can we get rid of that damn frisbee?
Making noise.
Two...
out of three.
And the last one is on the left.
So how are we gonna do that?
I guess I have to go...
back up there.
Fucking vines!
Yeah!
Skills to pay the bills!
Damn it.
That was actually so pro.
So if I...
If I...
Oh, we can't get any further with that.
Okay.
And if I go...
Okay, this is actually impossible then.
You literally can't do this.
Let me go back.
Oh!
Didn't mean to do that.
Fuck.
Jump!
Okay, we didn't need to...
Bubble there.
Hmm.
Oh, wait.
What if I...
Do this here?
Yeah!
That changed.
Oh!
Okay, okay.
I see, I see.
Easy.
Right!
Okay.
So now we gotta make a little bit more room.
Nope.
The other way.
Beautiful!
And now we just go back!
Hoi!
That is so risky.
Oh, wait a second.
We have a problem here.
No, we don't.
Yeah!
I inadvertently made a little room here for myself.
I didn't mean to, but I'm glad I did.
Yeah!
Look at that!
Wonderful!
Okay.
Sick.
Dude, I really like this puzzle.
This area is awesome.
The wheel is awesome.
I like the wheel.
It has...
It has brought me good fortune.
No, it has brought me good fortune.
Fuck me, dude.
Are you serious?
Take it slow.
Don't die now.
There's no reason to rush.
Oof.
A brick egg.
Nice.
A slick egg.
Uh...
Alrighty then!
Looks like this one is...
Done and dusted!
But...
Maybe we give it a quick glance.
Or destructible...
Thingamajigs.
I don't see anything.
Cool!
So we get the hell out of here.
Or...
Hmm...
No.
Okay.
I'm gonna make my exit now.
Get it?
Yeah!
Why is it so hard to do?
Okay, that's actually...
Ah!
Not bad.
Wait, how do I get out?
Oh, I should have moved the wheel.
Okay.
We may not have to go back here anyway.
So you know what?
Let's just teleport.
Let's go...
Where...
Okay, so what should I do next?
Do we have any other slots somewhere?
Let's remove these as well.
Clean up the map a bit, you know?
Keep our station clean.
Let's have a look.
Bare one.
Why did I make a circle here?
I must have had a reason.
You know what?
I'm gonna...
Leave that.
There's definitely another place with a slot.
I know there was.
Color wall.
Slot, slot, slot.
Did I not write it?
Uh...
Oh, I can't see my text.
Oh, I can, I can.
Okay.
It's very hard to see though.
Dude!
Did I not write it down?
Oh!
Let's remove this as well.
Don't need that anymore.
It will only confuse.
Right, there's this slot here.
Or not slot, spot.
But I wonder if there is a slot here.
There was something I couldn't access, remember?
I took the shark to here and there was something going on there.
And how do I get there?
I had the theory that I have to come from the left.
Meaning...
Here.
But how?
I'm not sure.
How many eggs do I have?
52.
So, I think there's 64 eggs to be found.
Given the, you know, multiply by 2 every time rule.
Oh!
Maybe we can break the skulls with the wheel!
That could be something, right?
Also, I made a little mark here for some reason.
Forgot why I did that.
What's the best way down here again?
Is it R?
No, no.
It's actually via the elevator.
So, bear one.
Bear one.
That's this one.
Also, while I'm traversing these old regions, I kind of want to see...
if there's anything else I can break.
Either with the wheel...
or with the spinny-spin.
What the fuck am I doing?
Come on.
Okay, so I gotta go...
right and then up.
Through the, uh, the egg room.
Look at all these beautiful eggs I've collected.
Yo, isn't this game just like...
Easter.
Look at all these colored eggs.
It's, it's, it's an egg hunt.
Like Easter.
That's what this game is.
Okay, I have a, I have a prediction.
There's gonna be an egg called a chocolate egg.
Somewhere.
That would be so fitting.
That looks breakable!
Brickety-brack!
Let me wheel...
and deal.
No?
What?
Oh, wait a minute.
I don't know what just happened.
Never mind.
Okay, so this right here...
Maybe I can say, uh, fuck off.
I am the new wheeler.
I wheel!
No?
Yeah, go up here.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Until we get to, all the way up there.
And then we go the elevator express.
Upwards.
Yike!
Okay.
Let's not forget, if I fuck up, I can always do the downward bubble.
I hereby command you to turn off.
Oh wait, that's not how we do it.
Uh...
There we go.
Now, what about this donut?
Uh, why did it go here again?
Oh yeah, skulls.
Skulls, skulls, skulls.
Oh, come on.
Please, please work.
Oh, no!
Dude...
What?
Really?
Damn.
Okay.
That's too bad.
Well, what then?
What then?
Shit.
Where have I not been very much?
I guess it's been a while since I've been up here on the top right.
We can go back up there and just sort of...
look around.
I gotta find, uh...
A door.
I gotta find a door.
And I gotta find a candle.
Cause I have a match.
Okay, I'm gonna assume that there's two more items to be found here.
Right?
That makes sense.
What did I say?
Bear...
Bear two.
Okay.
Nice.
That's this one.
So what am I looking for?
I'm looking for, uh, a possible candle.
Breakable floors.
And a gavelin.
Can we have a gavelin?
That actually looks breakable here.
No?
What about down here?
Is this?
You bastard!
Okay, uh...
Do you like my wheel?
I'm not protected from that while I'm wheeling.
Okay.
Damn you.
Damn you!
Okay.
Ah!
There's something right here on the other side, man.
Maybe that's what I should be focusing on.
Uh...
So there is, like, a little entrance.
It looks like here.
But I forgot exactly how that...
Or what the situation there was when I was there last.
Cause I remember going here and thinking, Oh, this is not it.
Or something similar.
Like I couldn't do anything.
Um...
The best way to get there is Bear 3.
Bear 3...
Oh, it's actually really close too.
Let's do it.
Nice.
Bear 3 is up here.
Oh, I think I know what it is.
So Bear 3 is basically like a brown bear.
That's the thing, right?
And the other ones are like polar bears or something.
Like different breeds of bears.
Save.
Alright, here we go.
Time to fly.
Can I...
I cannot wheel here for sure.
But can I deal?
Damage.
Yay!
Look at me go.
Wait, I'm seeing a potential entrance up north there.
Hold up.
Oh, this is...
Oh, this is here.
I was in the wrong spot.
Whoops.
But I'm seeing something right here.
The question is how do I get it?
Maybe if I'm fast enough.
Oh, check this out.
Ah!
Okay, wait.
Oh, yeah.
This is how we do it.
Of course.
We just use bubbles.
But is the...
Is the fish gonna get me?
Don't get me.
Oh, the vines.
Fuck!
That scared me!
Oh, my God.
Wow!
Fuckin' hell!
I thought I was high enough.
Uh...
Fuck.
I don't know then.
We gotta be faster with this.
Yes!
Sick!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That's breakable?
Whoa.
Safe.
Holy shit.
Wow!
Mega juicy, uh, thingy.
Yeah, look at my circle.
Ha, ha, ha!
Exactly where I predicted there would be an area.
Fantastic.
Um, okay.
I guess we got a wheel here.
Wheel and deal.
What just happened there?
Huh?
Ah!
Okay, there we go.
But, but, but wait.
How do we...
Wait a sec.
Something's wrong here.
I sense an issue.
Isn't this just gonna let me...
Oh!
Okay.
Uh, I saw breakable floor, but in the ceiling.
And, wait.
Is that, is that actually indicating breakable floor when it's like light blue?
You see that little there?
There's no way, right?
I wonder if I can go through here.
Break that and...
Oh, wait.
But why, what would the point be there?
Hmm.
Let's try this once more.
Ah, shit.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Let's go!
Sweet.
Wait, can I...
Break!
Oh!
Fuck me.
I...
Wait, what?
How?
Is this possible?
Uh...
Wait a sec.
Oh, wait a sec.
Maybe we can...
No, no, no.
Hmm.
I think I gotta...
I gotta come from up here.
Which means I gotta come from here.
So there's something I'm missing in this region.
Either that, or I need to somehow...
With lightning speed, get on the wheel.
Uh, while on the wheel, jump in the air.
Switch to bubble.
Apply the bubble, jump up, and then back to wheel.
But how the fuck are you gonna do that without keybinds?
I can't sit there scrolling through my items mid-air.
It's impossible.
Is it impossible?
How far away is...
Yeah, it's way too far away.
Also, I gotta try this, uh, fireworks...
More...
On things.
Yeah, by the...
This seems impossible to me.
Now, this right here is breakable for sure.
So maybe there is some kind of...
Thing going on here.
And to get there, it's also bear three.
So maybe I just go back.
There we go.
Bear three.
And then from here, we wanna go up and to the left.
Meanwhile, we're looking for breakable ground.
And we're gonna scan, of course.
Oh yeah.
Right.
No!
Ah, dammit.
What?!
I forgot how I did this.
How the...
Fuck did I do this?
What?
Uh...
Wait a sec.
Oh!
Right!
Okay.
I see now.
Ha!
We don't even need to move the other one, of course.
There we go.
Uh, okay, now.
Oh, yeah, I see the breakable!
No, wait, do I?
Oh, it's part of the...
Whale!
We can't even get in there.
Damn!
Well, that's a rip.
That's a mega rip.
Ha!
Uh, but...
There's definitely something going on here, right?
And to get there, something happens over here.
Let me make it a bit smaller.
Like there.
Even though it's not apparent from the map.
Uh, bear two.
I think.
Is that the best way?
Bear two...
It's gonna be kind of an annoying path, but let's just do it.
Maybe we'll find other things on the way.
Bear two!
Coming in!
Blibble!
Ah!
There we go.
Bear two!
Yep.
Bear two.
Okay, uh, I'm gonna take a quick break, actually.
It's been, uh, over one and a half hours.
I'm gonna hydrate myself and stuff.
Um, I'm gonna go up here, and then to that spot, and see if I can't find a way.
I'll see you in a bit.
And we're back.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's do the left side, and then up, and then right.
What?
That's the plan.
Stupid bird ain't gonna ruin my day.
Now, oh, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This place is actually kinda...
Look now, we can do this.
There's gotta be something here, no?
Now that we have this...
You can't tell me there's nothing.
Maybe not.
Is that a little koala?
Look at that!
Hanging on the pillar.
Uh, what am I looking for?
A path.
Uh, is this the right way up here?
I think it is.
Also, I'm not really paying attention.
Maybe there's a breakable floor somewhere.
Nope.
Not that I can see.
Okay.
Ah, goddammit.
Oh, what's that?
What's that?
Oh, nevermind.
Okay.
We can also save here.
Maybe I should.
Get that.
Evil spirits.
Brian is here.
I'm looking for any type of path.
In the ceiling or...
In the floor.
Anywhere.
Wait, why do we have a...
Oh, there's a little bit of interesting stuff here.
Uh...
What?
Huh?
I'm in a wheel!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
God, do I have to do this?
No, really?
Is that the only way?
So that does this.
That does that.
There.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Ah.
Fucked it up.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Nooooo!
Damn.
Nice.
Ah!
I think I fell for the same thing...
As last time.
Wait, what is the point of doing this then?
I guess there is no point.
There we go.
Okay, okay.
Oh, yeah, this spot!
Ooh!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
A minute.
We can definitely do something here.
Knowing that we have this...
No, wait, uh...
This mapping.
Right?
Uh, let's see.
So...
Oh, god, this is gonna be so hard to do.
I guess I'm just gonna write the combination down.
So we have...
Uh, let me see.
Whoops.
We have sad...
Happy.
Sad...
Happy would be...
Let me just see here.
Sad is that one.
That's five.
Uh...
Actually, maybe it's easier if we just do...
Yeah.
That's actually better.
Uh...
Arrow up.
And then...
Uh...
Happy.
Seven.
Plus down.
Uh...
In fact, let me just do it...
Do it like this.
It's gonna be easier.
I cannot figure out my keybinds right now.
Jesus Christ.
There we go.
Okay, so up, down...
And what then?
Then we do...
Sad again.
Happy again.
Okay.
Uh...
Sad.
Happy.
Uh...
Weird face.
And happy weird face.
Six.
Which is this way.
And happy weird face.
That's eight.
Which is this.
What then?
Then we have...
Okay, it's the same again.
So it's...
Here, here.
Okay.
Here we go.
I'm gonna try and do it while I look at this.
Uh...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Here we go.
So it's...
Up.
Down.
Left.
Right.
Really?
Wait a sec.
Sad.
Happy.
That is definitely...
Up.
Down.
Sad.
Happy.
And then we have...
Six.
Eight.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's it.
I don't get it.
Maybe I need to be inside.
Uh...
The way to get inside is to...
Right.
We gotta lure...
Brian.
Come here.
Okay.
Okay, now.
Here we go.
They should do it, right?
What?!
No way.
Maybe it's the other way.
Hmm.
Maybe it's, uh...
Oh, wait.
Okay, so we have a combination over here.
And a picture of...
A demon on the left.
Notice, by the way, that the demon is surrounded by...
Contour lines with bubbles in them.
What is the point here?
What's going on?
What is going on here?
Will the light reveal a secret?
Like, you cannot tell me that this is not...
This!
Sad, happy, sad, happy.
Weird, happy, weird, happy.
But a different kind of happy.
Hmm.
I'm reading from left to right.
Bro.
Like, I refuse to leave here!
This has to be it!
What do you mean it's not it?!
What else could it be?!
Also, this is the room, apparently, that will somehow connect to the room on the other side.
Although I can't, for the life of me, see how that's gonna work.
Like, how are we gonna get over there?
From here?
How?
Uh, I'm gonna ride demon here.
The demon!
Demon.
Look how...
Evil that demon is.
That sly smile, you know, and mischievous...
Look in the eye.
Okay.
What am I missing?
Oh no, we're gonna listen to that now, forever.
Do I...
Can I remote control the Chihuahua?
Fuck it.
Okay, so now we're back here.
Well, that's kind of a disappointment there.
I'm not gonna lie.
Like, how is that not the solution to whatever's going on, you know?
Uh, what do I look for now?
I'm running out of ideas here.
Also, my cables are all over the place.
Let me just fix that.
There we go.
Okay.
I gotta figure out how to make this controller wireless.
On the computer.
Maybe I need a dongle or something.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait!
Oh, I thought there was a cipher in the back there.
With the dice.
But they're just, uh, windows or something?
Oh, you know what this probably is?
This is glass.
That's what those blocks are.
Uh, what was this place?
Wait, didn't we also have a, uh, a cryo chamber or something?
There was some...
Oh, I forgot the name of it.
There was something somewhere.
Oh god, was it in here?
Some kind of chamber.
Also, there's this weird, uh, cat-looking room.
And this area here...
Okay, we gotta investigate that.
I did make a circle here.
For a reason.
So maybe we go back there.
Which is...
Which way is that?
F1.
We can do that.
Okay, I'm gonna try something.
While I'm here...
Acha!
Maybe it is telling me that I need to make that song somewhere else.
Maybe a place that is, uh, related to the demon picture.
F1 is here.
Okay, now I wanna be on the lookout for breakable floors.
And secret paths.
Yeah.
Also, I could try going down here again.
Is that something I wanna do?
What was down there?
Oh, is that the place where I put the question marks?
I think it may have been.
Okay.
Just...
Do the lazy path here.
Oh yeah, I can just...
Shoot it down, right?
Yeah, much better.
Okay.
So what am I missing in this area?
Yeah.
Supposedly something up there.
Oh!
I found it already.
I didn't remove this.
Okay.
Nevermind.
But is there more?
Breakable floors?
The breakable floors are gonna be the end of me because they're so hard to spot, dude.
It's so difficult.
There's a sea of textures.
It's just...
I can't.
This room...
Has a telephone.
Is there anything else?
Also, I should remember that I have a wheel.
So...
Oh yeah, we gotta look for more slots.
For that.
Because there was definitely more than one slot.
I think I just didn't note it down when I saw it.
And this right here.
Oh god, what was it?
There was a...
A cube.
With a...
With some kind of animal.
Long-legged animal was on this.
An evil long-legged animal.
Remember?
And we needed to do something...
To affect that.
That's also a thing.
And the color wall.
Well, since I'm here...
Let's just go room by room and experiment with the new toys we have.
Oh yeah, I'm safe with this everywhere.
Oh, that's actually such a nice relief.
I don't have to worry about anything.
So, top left is definitely a secret, but we found that already, I believe.
Did we?
I see vines...
That cover something.
No, yeah, I definitely found that.
I remember.
Okay.
This is the bubble region.
Bubble, bubble, bubble region.
I feel like there's gotta be more secrets in this area.
You could hide a million things here.
Oh!
Oh, I forgot about the...
Shit.
Crap!
I don't know where to go!
I wanna go back to fish one.
I hate this place.
This is gonna be painful, by the way.
Wait a sec.
Oh, it just occurred to me as well.
Look at the backgrounds on each of these, uh...
Fast travel systems.
They have the corresponding sort of biome behind them.
That's kinda neat, I just noticed.
That's cool.
Now, lantern time.
Perhaps.
Oh, yeah!
I forgot I did that!
Ha!
Wait!
Hello!
No fucking way.
Well, that was lucky.
That was completely unintended.
Why am I doing this?
Wait a sec.
Why...
Why am I doing this?
How do...
Wait.
How the fuck?
Do I get in there?
Oh, god.
The wheel is difficult to control.
Oops, I didn't mean to.
God dammit.
Wait, what was that?
This is impossible.
I'm so bad at this game.
Come on.
There we go.
Now, take me out of here before I lose my mind.
These sounds.
Okay.
So what do I...
How the fuck do I get down there?
Looks like from above somehow.
Oops.
Do I destroy the floor here?
Dude, I have no idea.
Like, my instinct is to ride the disc, but there's no room.
Is there?
Oh!
There's...
Dude.
That was the first thought I had, but then I dismissed it immediately?
Because it looked like there was not enough room.
It looked like there was just enough room for the disc and not me.
For fuck's sake.
Galaxy egg!
Nice!
I like that.
God dammit.
I should just try things from now on.
But I was so convinced that wouldn't work.
Okay.
Bubble me.
And then on the way down, we're gonna try and play with this.
Wow, that actually briefly revealed the chest too.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah!
Made it.
Now...
Why am I here?
What am I doing?
Hmm.
I don't know what I'm looking for.
Oh, don't do that.
That's gonna fuck me.
Wait, I sense a secret here?
Yeah!
Check this out.
You ready?
Oh, wait a sec.
Can I just...
Never mind.
I think I just realized.
Yeah, okay.
I see.
I thought I could be...
Or break the wall up top and get inside of that little enclosure.
And maybe something would happen.
But there's just a burp.
It's a burp.
Okay.
Now I'm here.
Gavilan time?
I smell breakable floors.
Oh!
Careful there, buddy.
Wait, whoa!
Oh!
Oh, wait.
I've been there.
Why can't I fucking...
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
I lit this one.
We gotta find more candles, man.
Where the hell could they be?
Oh, wait.
I see a potential secret.
That's just...
Okay, okay.
What is the point of that?
Hmm.
I'm not sensing anything here.
Oh, my God.
I'm dying now, too.
Now I'm back in this region.
Yeah, I don't wanna be here.
Dude, I feel so goddamn aimless in this game.
It's crazy.
Like, I don't wanna backtrack through every single piece of region in this game.
I feel like there's gotta be some way to guide me in some specific way here.
Like, otherwise, it's just ridiculous.
If I...
If I'm expected to just backtrack through every single region...
That sounds insane.
I mean, we still have this up here.
But, uh, that looks...
Like I said, impossible.
Like, look at this here!
There's an opening there for sure.
That has to come from the right side!
Oh, you know what?
Maybe the, uh, demon puzzle is related to somehow...
If I do this, maybe that opens a door over here.
Or something.
Do...
Okay, so do we know of a demon?
Somewhere.
Long-eared demon...
Oh!
Could be here!
Actually...
Wait a sec, where was that?
Where was that mural?
Uh...
Here!
So, to get there...
Bear 1...
Yeah.
Let's just...
Let's just do it.
Because I am pretty lost right now.
Uh...
Bear 1...
What's up, Brian?
Also, let me try and...
They see me rolling...
They hating...
Maybe I break some stuff on my way in...
It's actually a great way to just test the ground for breakables.
Wait a second...
I may have had this, uh, test before.
Maybe even multiple times, but...
Fuck it, I'm trying it again.
I see a little path here.
I may have been there before.
Yeah, I've been there.
Okay.
Alright.
Wait, what was that?
Oh, telephone.
Yeah, save the game, actually.
So, uh, to the right.
In fact, let's just try this combination everywhere we go.
Um...
Ah, Doc!
Check it out.
Demon Doc!
What?!
No way!
That actually worked!
That was so fucking random!
Wait, I must have skipped some hints or something.
Because I just accidentally did something I didn't even intend to do.
What the fuck?!
Like...
At this point, I'm just trying to understand how would you, uh...
Even come to that conclusion that you needed to do that.
That was so fucking random.
Random.
Yeah, I don't... I don't know.
That was so weird.
Uh, I'm gonna write, um...
Mural.
Dude, what are the chances?!
I've had a similar, uh, experience recently in Blueprints as well, where something like that happened.
I kinda hate when it does, but I guess it's the risk when you play puzzle games.
Like, that wasn't satisfying to me now, because now I don't know why that worked.
I don't see the leap of logic here.
At all.
Unless...
This combination is like a global thing that you can use at different areas.
And you can do things.
So, so that duck was turned into...
A bunny.
And it jumped off.
Maybe that's what this is.
Oh, this actually looks like a bunny.
The tail is weird though.
Looks like a dick.
That can't be right.
I was joking about the last part.
I'm kidding, come on.
Come on now.
Okay, what's next?
Uh, well that's...
That's fucking done and dusted, I think.
There may be more related to that combination.
But, uh, let's just keep an eye out here.
Um...
Why did I make a little skull here?
Let's investigate!
Why did I make a skull?
How do I get back here?
What is my name?
Where do I come from?
Oh no, I gotta go through this place again then.
Oh, I'm actually sort of close.
Actually, okay, I see the logical leap now.
It's the same leap I made.
This kinda looks like the picture, right?
This creature right here.
I think it's a bunny.
That kinda looks...
Like the one up there.
So, you know, the hint is you gotta be somewhere here.
I guess.
Also, what is...
Oh, nevermind, okay.
Down.
Down, down, down.
Right.
Down.
Okay.
And we're gonna be wheeling and dealing as we go along.
Wait, I'm smelling a destructible floor here.
No?
Okay.
Wait, why did I make a...
thing here?
Remove it.
Oh!
Oh, I know now!
When I was here last time, something was chasing me and I had to hide in these tunnels.
So, I marked it as deadly.
Basically.
That's what happened.
Um...
Okay.
What about here?
This place looks like...
Something is going on, doesn't it?
Hup!
Okay.
Breakable?
No breakable.
Go down.
Check for chests.
What am I seeing?
There's gotta be a secret on the way down here.
I refuse to believe it.
There's a flower growing on the wall on the left there.
All the textures look the same on the walls.
Okay, so now...
Oh, so now I'm here.
Well, let's just keep investigating.
Save the game.
Beepity boop.
There's something behind the waterfall.
I love the wheel.
Hup!
Ah!
I tried to do a trick shot there.
Trick jump.
Am I seeing anything?
I...
don't.
Wait.
Like, tell me that wall on the right doesn't look breakable!
Okay, whatever.
Take me up.
Oh no, this spot again.
Okay, can I at least see some kind of path?
Not really.
Do I even wanna be here?
I hate this place.
With a passion.
Now, it looks like there's something down here, but there's not.
Is there?
No, isn't that...
That's right below me.
Wait, I'm so confused.
There's...
There's definitely something down there.
Oh, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Ho!
Egg!
Sapphire egg, bitch!
Yeah!
Okay, sick!
Very nice.
Dude, I'm killing it right now.
I forgot I could do that.
Sweet!
Okay, okay.
We gotta find more spots where we couldn't normally progress because of these damn burps.
And use the light.
To banish them to the shadow realm.
So if I do that here, they're gonna...
Right?
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe there's a secret here.
Are these burps a secret?
Somehow.
Wow.
What about the remote?
Dude, imagine, though, a Chihuahua.
But remote-controlled.
And the crazy thing is, like, a remote control on its own is not that impressive.
Neither is the Chihuahua.
But together, they form something greater than its sum, you know?
Or the sum is greater than its parts.
Take me up, please.
Thank you.
I always find myself back here in this region for some reason.
Why did I put a question mark here?
Oh!
We gotta remove it.
This is a question mark because, uh...
I wasn't solving this, but now I did solve it, so that goes away.
Yes.
I speak English very well.
Now...
Perhaps Bear 2 is an order.
This place...
I have not been to for quite a while.
Yeah.
Let's just go there and revisit and see what's going on, you know?
It's been a while.
I like it.
Uh...
Do I...
Wait, which way do I go?
Kinda wanna go up.
And I guess I can.
Show me the chests.
Fucking burps.
Oh, I don't wanna hit that button.
There's so many burps here.
Oh...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No...
No.
I was thinking we could use the light, but what would that...
give me there?
Not really anything.
Can I banish you guys?
To the Shadowlands?
You like the wheel?
Whee!
Yeah, what if I...
What if I hit the button and then quickly go...
See ya, nerds!
Aha!
They're mad!
Nerds!
That feels good.
That feels really good.
Wait, what's this place?
Ooh!
Haven't been here in a while.
I guess I can just walk down here!
Isn't that cool?
I'm looking for...
Oh, wait, I may see a little hidden secret!
Oh, no, that's where I dropped down, I guess.
Okay, so we did this one.
That's breakable!
Breakable, breakable!
Breakable.
Right there.
So we gotta get above.
And we do that by going all the way back.
Shit.
But...
Isn't that just gonna break me down to where I am now?
But okay, you know, maybe there's more to it.
It's kind of a nice baseline.
If I play my flute while that happens, that could be kind of dope.
See you later, nerds!
Ooi, that was close!
That was close indeed.
Here.
Left.
Save.
Now, I feel like there's gotta be something here, because I have the light now and I can banish all these fools.
That should count for something.
Right?
In any case, we gotta go up.
I'm getting deja vu here.
Yeah, I've been here today.
Just go this way.
So what was the deal here?
Not go this way?
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, I've been here today.
What the fuck am I talking about, about not having been here for a while?
That was straight up untrue.
To be fair though, a lot of these regions just look exactly alike.
I really should be...
Be beleaping.
Whenever I can, to see if there's any chests.
Okay.
Aren't these bastards gonna appear now?
Oh, not this again.
Actually...
I wanna give this another look, since I'm here.
May as well do it.
First...
I'm gonna nail it first try.
Yes!
Good.
How is that not connecting to the left?
Reveal thyself.
Reveal!
Gavlan wheel.
Gavlan reveal.
Gavlan needs a meal.
Let me through.
Open up, open something up.
Do it for me.
There's nothing.
Dude, the sound of the wheel rolling is really satisfying.
Alright, this one is a dead end.
Literally.
Get rid of that.
Uh...
Let's go back here and see if we can't figure that out.
Because...
That should be doable.
That's bear...
Three.
We should be able to figure something out there.
Unless I need an item.
Maybe...
Hold on.
Maybe I need an item up there that I don't have.
I can see that.
Actually.
I can see it.
Uh...
What outstanding issues do we have?
Color wall?
We could check that out again.
Wait a minute.
I wonder...
So, this is the candle location.
I wonder if the location of the candles in this matrix...
correspond to the locations I found...
the candles on the map.
You know what I mean?
Like approximately, like northwest, east, south...
stuff like that.
Hmm...
I don't know.
In any case, I wanna try this again here.
Just really quickly give it a look.
Uh...
Not here.
We gotta go up.
Yup!
Oh, I made it.
Nice.
Look at these stones right here.
That's the stone that I saw...
Ah, somewhere.
Some...
Oh wait.
I'm gonna grab this while I'm here.
Bum...
Oh, what's the time?
17.47.
Okay.
I wonder if...
Uh...
So, on the clock, it said 5-2, right?
I wonder if... I'm trying to think.
5-2... Oh, but that would be 17 o'clock.
I don't know.
Never mind.
I don't know what I'm thinking.
Fog it.
Left side.
What am I... Oops.
Flick the switch!
There we go.
Okay.
No!
It was downstairs!
Fuck!
Why did I think it was up here?
Wait, what is that changing?
Look at this.
We got a receiver.
I don't know.
Something is changing.
Sick!
But I rolled on my wheel here.
It didn't destroy anything.
What the hell?
I was on my wheel here.
I tested it.
Oh, wait a second.
Hold the phone.
Oh, wait.
I see.
Oh, no.
No, I don't see.
I don't see.
I am so confused.
What's the secret here?
And what...
What's this...
Doing?
What's the point?
Can I use my...
What the...
Fuck?
What is the point of this?
And what is my remote doing?
I have no clue what's happening here.
Like, at all.
What is going on?
I don't get it.
What is going on here?
Is there more I can destroy here?
Something about these bricks here.
It's very interesting.
I don't know.
I guess I'll come back.
I have no idea.
I think I may need something, or I...
My brain can't figure it out.
Uh, okay.
What's next?
Right, I wanted to go left.
That was the whole point.
Alright, we gotta go back up here.
Because something's happening.
And there's gotta be a way to do it.
Whatever's going on.
Oh god.
Wait, how did I do this?
Oh yeah.
Bubble.
No.
Nice.
Sweetness.
Yoink.
Once more.
Up.
What?
Why am I so bad at this suddenly?
That should be it.
Look how high we are.
Whop.
There we go.
Okay.
Now.
Save the game.
Maybe...
Hold on.
Maybe I just go for...
A good old...
Oh no.
I can't even do that.
The vines!
Uh...
Hmm.
Oh, that is so weird.
The way that works.
Whoa!
That feels so wrong.
Can I...
Yeah!
No.
Let me see here.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
It's six!
You can't do that in one jump.
Oh, wait a sec.
Is it...
Why don't we just do this?
Oh shit.
Uh...
That's...
Wow, that's impossible.
I don't know.
That's not going to do anything.
So, if I have to go...
Up by this way and not come down...
The only way to traverse the spikes...
Is to use...
Either a wheel...
Like this.
Actually, wait a minute.
I'm noticing that my character is sort of...
Being accelerated upwards as I...
Break.
Maybe I can...
Slingshot myself somehow?
Is that a thing?
If I...
Can I do that in the air?
Let me see.
I roll.
I roll and I go...
Oh!
Okay, I'm getting a little more height.
Oh shit.
Does that change anything?
Oh, wait a minute.
One, two, three...
Oh no, it's way too far away!
Unless we can...
Fucking vines are ruining the day.
Maybe with enough bubbles...
They're going to traverse left somehow?
Push each other left?
No?
How on earth?
Jump?
I need to practice.
So, if I'm on a wheel...
Okay, it's the same height.
Almost.
What if I were to...
Can I hit the lamp?
Ah, I can't bounce off the lamp.
Unfortunately.
Oh wait, I have an idea.
One, two, three, four...
Push the bubbles!
Oh!
I tried to push the bubbles left...
Then jump on the bubbles at the end.
Okay, I think it's just impossible...
To do it the way I'm trying to do it.
You can't...
You can't get enough height...
Doing that.
You need something...
To elevate you up...
As you go, right?
Oh, wait a sec, actually.
I just had an idea.
Can you...
Apply...
A wheel in the air...
And then another wheel?
That seems exploity.
Huh!
Oops.
Didn't mean to do that.
Haha!
That looks so funny.
Can I some more...
Bounce off the wall and then...
No?
Okay.
Ha!
Can I catch up to a disc?
If I'm fast enough.
I guess I can...
Push these vines out of the way.
Cuckoo!
How do I push those out of the...
If I can push the vines out of the way...
Maybe with this...
No?
Can I somehow place something?
In between to...
Does it bounce...
Wait, does it bounce off a bubble?
Oh, wait.
Don't break.
No, it goes through.
Okay.
How on earth?
Oh!
Okay, okay.
I got it a little higher.
Maybe if I...
Oh!
This...
This doesn't feel intended.
I feel like I'm once again janking the game, you know?
Haha!
Yeah, this is janky as hell.
But you know what?
Sometimes a little jank is just what the doctor ordered here.
Oh!
You can't tell me that's not...
Close.
Haha!
Yeah!
Nope.
Okay.
I...
Bro!
I'm losing my mind.
I'm getting the same vibes as when I tried to do this.
Remember the region?
With the box that I couldn't get to because there were spikes on the floor?
It's like...
I feel like I need another item just like that, you know?
Oh, that was so...
That was so high up, though.
What I just did.
Vines!
Dude!
Like, let's say I even do get the disc...
There's no way I can even get back on the disc.
That's the problem.
It needs to be super high up.
It needs to be at least the height of...
Well, here.
My max height here, above the lamp.
You know?
And that just can't be done.
I think I gotta get behind it and then push it to the left instead of pushing it to the right.
Yep.
Like that, and then quickly switch back.
Switch back.
Nope.
Not quite.
Can I just displace them with bubbles?
No, no.
Of course they break.
Oh!
That was close!
Oi!
Oi, oi, oi!
I think.
Okay, so now I'm here.
Okay, let me try...
Yep!
What if I'm fast enough?
Oi!
I mean, maybe, actually.
But I'd have to go like...
Ah!
Oh, actually, that almost looks like...
You can do it.
Oi!
Maybe here.
Nope.
Come on!
Fuck me, dude!
This is ins...
You cannot catch up to that.
Okay, hold on.
Let me try it in a different area where we have more like...
So if I just run...
What if I disc first and then jump?
No.
Jump disc.
That's better.
Oh, that was close.
I'm totally janking.
I'm kind of close.
I'm going to catch up to it!
What the
f...
Maybe...
Oh, but what if I use...
The speed of this to my advantage?
Hey!
Ah!
Damn!
Give up!
Nope.
Like, I feel like in here I'm kind of close to doing it.
So basically what I'm trying...
I'm trying to throw the disc...
Whoop!
And then fucking land on it before...
It bounces off, you know?
Maybe I need to...
Can I speed myself up somehow?
Do I get enough momentum?
I need to practice in a different place.
Unless this is a...
Pffft...
Waste of time.
Like, basically...
If you gotta do it, you gotta do the disc...
Uh...
Right at the end of the jump.
You know, like...
Okay, not that late, but...
You know what I mean?
That's impossible.
Yeah.
You can't do it.
And even if it is possible...
It's gonna be unintended.
That is just not intended at all.
From a game design perspective...
That makes zero sense.
Jump.
Ah!
What am I even doing here?
Maybe I should just...
Go back?
Actually...
I wanna check out the bottom part of this.
Go.
Uh...
Yeah.
Safe.
Whoop!
Didn't mean to fall.
Oh!
Doggo!
It's been a while.
What's going on, brother?
What's happening?
Oh, I can't even get to you.
How did I...
Get in here?
I guess I'm not getting in there.
Unless I go...
Around.
Sup!
Wow, he didn't even see me.
Okay, so what's going on here?
This is...
This is intriguing, isn't it?
Look at these.
Oh!
Yeah!
Ah!
Fuck!
That scared me!
Holy shit!
That came out of nowhere!
Oh!
There he is!
Look at his heart beating!
Uh...
Okay, so what do I gotta do here?
I want to scare him off, but I can't.
Hmm.
Can I just use a disc?
Disc me.
Actually, I can.
This is gonna be super...
No!
Doggo!
No, no, no, no, no!
You're not supposed to grab that!
Fucking sake.
Yep!
See ya!
See ya, buddy!
Oh, doggos.
Fuck me.
Uh, what am I even doing?
Goddamn.
Uh...
Well, that's not the way I want it to go.
I want it to go down.
What am I even doing?
Ah!
No!
Okay.
Oh, they're chasing the disc.
Nice.
Oh, the guy's gone.
Okay, nice.
Alright.
Let's do...
So, I got to go through here.
I want to get to the cat face room.
Which is over there.
Can I do it in a better way other than just that?
You know what?
Ah!
Hey, that works.
Not bad.
I have a remote for this, sir.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, I'm gonna need the fucking...
Scrabble book.
I don't know why I said that.
I need the thing that goes...
Okay, so hold on.
I'm seeing potential breakable wall on the left.
Am I crazy?
What's that?
Oh, not.
Why am I here?
Oh!
I needed to go down and then right.
Whoops.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Shit!
Uh, what do I do?
What do I do?
Oh, wait.
Did I just kill it with the lamp?
Nice!
That's awesome.
Didn't know you could do that.
Whoops.
Oh.
Fuck.
Yo, can you get me in the wheel?
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You can't get me in the wheel!
Gavilan wheels and he deals and you cannot get in...
...to get a meal.
Um...
Oh.
Up here.
There we go.
Like, something's going on here, no?
This room is way too mysterious.
Ah, maybe not.
Maybe it's...
...exactly what it looks like.
I'm tempted to just go on the map and just sort of cross it off as don't come back here, but...
...if there is something in there, then I'm shooting myself in the foot, right?
That's the problem.
I'm still on the lookout for, uh...
Oh, shit.
Take the disc!
There we go.
I wanna find slots for my wheel!
Goddammit!
I should've marked it when I saw it!
There was more than one slot.
I just don't remember where.
Maybe it was down here, actually.
Let's go to R.
There we go.
R is down here.
Oh, yeah.
Here.
Scary region.
But I have the light.
What?
Okay, so this place.
Yeah.
I remember.
Just grab that for later.
What am I even looking for right now?
I... I'm just sort of aimlessly wandering.
Ah!
A wheel!
Yes!
Yeah, dude!
And look, and would you...
Oh my god, look at this.
It's a secret on a secret.
Hold on.
Hahahaha!
You can't fool me!
Wait, is that just a shortcut, or what is that?
Maybe it's just a shortcut.
Oh...
Wait, what?
There's bricks.
Brickety Brack.
Would love a snack.
Oh, wait, wait.
I have an idea.
I got an idea.
Did that change anything?
No?
Okay.
Maybe I can jump up here.
It can't just have been a bit of food.
Like, I refuse to believe that.
There's more to this.
There is no freaking way.
I don't buy it.
You can't tell me.
It's just to get a little piece of food.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
There's also a...
Hold on.
We're not done.
Let me actually mark this before I forget.
We're gonna have...
A slot.
We're gonna make a little star.
To indicate that it still needs to be explored.
That's what that means.
There was also a similar door on the left, remember?
But I don't recall if there was a slot.
I think there may have been.
Wow, this is still in the same state that I left it, or...
Or what?
Wait, haven't I...
Oh, yeah, okay.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's above me.
It's not here.
Ah, I need to do this.
Slinky time.
No, wait, what, what?
Whoops.
That's not what I need to do.
To go...
Up here.
Yeah.
That's it.
This way.
Gonna eat this.
No, we're not gonna eat it.
Give me that.
Six out of six, damn.
We are ready for combat.
Crowd chamber!
Incubator!
That was the name.
Okay, so wait a minute.
Incubator?
That's something, uh...
That's like Jurassic Park style, right?
Isn't it?
Isn't that what they did in that movie?
We gotta do something like that here.
With eggs.
Oh, wait a...
Wait a minute.
We got these weird bricks again!
Something with those bricks.
The Brigity Brack is, uh...
It's not what we think it is.
Wait a sec.
Wasn't...
Wasn't there a big, uh...
Thing here?
Did I move that as...
Wait.
Oh, did I move that as well when I did the wheel?
Whoops.
How can I...
Use that to my advantage?
Okay, so I'm moving both of them when I turn that wheel over there in the slot.
Uh...
Also, there's gotta be something in here, I imagine.
Somehow.
Color wall is there.
That's in another region though.
How do I get in there?
Maybe via...
This room...
We can take another look there, I guess.
This room or that room.
It's gotta be one of the three.
Oh shit.
Uh...
Let me try and turn the wheel again.
Actually, we have a pretty easy path back.
Like...
Okay.
What is this?
Hello?
There's just no way that's it here.
I don't believe it.
Okay.
Now that it's in that configuration...
Let me just go take a look.
Who knows?
Maybe things are different.
Also, uh...
Notice how there's something above me here.
You see that?
Right here.
Like...
What's...
What's that all about?
We gotta get in there somehow.
Yeah!
Look!
There it is!
So we move that out of the way...
And then...
Something.
Damn.
Well...
Shit.
I don't know what to do.
What's this?
Inc...
So incubator...
Can I...
Can I incubate this?
I...
Don't know what I should be bringing here.
Some kind of egg.
I need to bring the master egg.
One egg to rule them all.
Uh...
Well, shit.
Let me try and get to, uh...
F2 region.
And...
Figure out what the hell's going on.
So fish two.
F2 is down here.
Uh...
There's two...
Where the fuck are these candles at?
I got no clue.
Okay, so I can't...
Oh, it's gotta be from this room if I gotta go down.
This room...
Where we started.
There's gotta be something here that breaks, no?
Do we need to use this?
Wait, what?
Okay.
No.
Nope.
Man, oh man.
That waterfall is suspicious.
No, it's not.
Not suspicious at all.
Oh, wait a minute!
There's also a...
Oh, where was that?
Something about fragments, remember?
We put something in somewhere.
In a place that looked like this, but I forgot.
What the name of it was.
Okay.
Wait, is this the place with the snake, or is that...
to the right?
I think it may be to the right of here.
Also, I'm constantly just...
looking for that glint, you know?
Uh...
Oh, here it is, yeah.
Maybe there's something I missed here.
We can try and destroy the...
Let's try and wheel and deal.
This little hole makes me...
Intrigued.
It's just water, okay.
Bro, please, get a...
Dude!
No!
We're back here?!
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Well...
Let's just explore here, I guess.
Oh, no, not...
Disc!
Ah!
Fuck you.
Catch.
Okay, so...
Okay, wait a minute.
Something was going on here, right?
I need to find this fucking creature.
Because I've seen it somewhere else as well.
We've got to deal with it somehow.
It's on the loose.
Maybe it has an egg up its ass.
And we've got to extract it.
What?
You know what I mean?
Where else have we seen this bastard?
Let me actually mark this.
LSP.
Last seen position.
Uh...
I think I also saw it...
Somewhere here.
In the area with, um...
Where you go up to the thingy.
Where is that?
I know exactly where it is.
Let me see here.
Goddammit, I can't find it!
Also, this...
This looks...
Interesting there.
Bro, am I...
Blind?
Bear one?
Dog, shut up!
Ohhhh!
Jesus Christ!
Why can't I find it?
I've been there a million times today!
Here!
Uh...
Last... last seen position.
LSP.
Let's go there.
Let's see if it's back there.
Remember, it was guarding.
It was standing right here.
Like a bastard.
Also, there's a chest here.
Let's not forget that.
Uh...
So this would be...
Is it really bear one?
To get to that?
Come on!
I'll bear one.
Uh...
B1.
Let's see how fast I can get there.
What's up, Brian?
See you later, Brian.
God, I want that chest up there so bad.
We gotta find eggs.
No, no, no.
I messed up.
The speed run is...
is...
dead now.
I was on such good track, you know?
To beat records.
Uh...
Let's see if the duck is back.
It's not, okay.
Oh wait, I went...
the wrong way.
Oh, it's L!
Jesus...
Christ!
That is so camouflaged there.
L is the...
bottom right.
My goodness.
It's not here!
Oh God.
Are we expected to just search the entire map now?
If there even is something to do with that?
Ah...
Bro.
I'm stopping here.
I don't feel like searching the entire map to find...
whatever it is...
right now.
We're gonna continue this next time.
That seems unfun.
To just search fucking every room...
to find...
a candle or whatever.
Oh...
Okay, I actually made it in good time.
I was planning to do three hours...
approximately.
Cause I gotta do some things.
Nice!
I timed it right.
I didn't even look at the time.
I somehow just felt it.
Ah, let's see here.
What's up guys?
Uh...
This...
This game right here is...
insanely difficult.
But I guess I am kind of doing...
extracurricular activities, right?
Like I beat the game already.
So there's...
that.
Oliver, please observe this...
What did you write?
Wait...
Why did it get...
sanctioned?
I was about to say.
Censored.
It is very meticulous.
Yeah, it is.
It's insane.
And just traversing the map itself is difficult.
You can't just go from A to B quite easily.
The well is deep indeed.
Yeah!
Actually.
I mean, if you think about it, the entire map is kind of a well.
Because if you take the 2D map and you sort of rotate it around the cylinder, you cyclic the path, right?
You go from left to right, so it kind of makes sense.
It's a 2D map wrapped around the 2D, uh, 3D cylinder.
And a cylinder is also a well!
And there's animals down there.
Animal donut.
Oh yeah!
Right!
Or a tor- yeah, torus, I guess is another way to say that.
Around a ball, because it goes from top to bottom too.
Oh yeah!
Actually, good point!
Good point.
Actually, you're more right than I am then.
I guess I just wanted it to fit neatly with the theory of it being a well.
A torus well.
Oh yeah, yeah!
For sure.
Left to right.
Oh yeah, you're right actually, because if you go to top right, you don't arrive in the bottom left to right.
So you're right.
Torus.
Makes more sense.
I was looking at Oliver's backlog.
What consoles does he have?
I have a Playstation.
A Switch.
And that's it.
I don't have an Xbox.
Or uh...
I also do have a Nintendo 64, but it's at my dad's.
And I kinda wanna...
Borrow it from him.
For reasons.
You'll find out soon.
Does the well make you unwell?
Uh, no.
Actually, I feel quite well right now.
I was unwell a couple days ago.
And yesterday.
I have no comment.
Uh...
I'm still enjoying the game.
I enjoy solving the little puzzles here and there.
But I'm probably gonna stop playing when I don't find any more, you know?
But I'm constantly finding new things.
It just...
takes a bit.
I'm not that frustrated.
I'm more frustrated at myself.
Not uh...
Having written down things on the map and stuff.
Like, I understand I'm doing extra stuff right now.
The game is over.
You know?
Like, I did beat the game.
I got credits.
So, you know, I did the thing.
I'm only basically squeezing the lemon for a bit more juice right now.
Because the juice is tasty.
But it's definitely getting a little less juice.
As time goes on, right?
Yeah, I'm ending now.
First name I could think of.
I can't believe you actually got that name.
Yeah, I made...
I made big progress here.
I got the...
I got the wheel.
I got the wheel and I started moving things with the wheel.
Your giant screen really makes it harder for you to see things.
Yeah, probably.
Because I have to move my head physically to go to different sections of the screen.
But it's nice.
I don't have great eyesight, so having a big screen is actually really nice for me.
Like, if it's too tiny, then it's just annoying and I get a headache, you know?
It's not that bad prescription.
It's like, uh, minus two.
Or something.
How big is your screen?
It's like 32 inches.
But the thing is, it's quite close to my face because it's just more comfortable for me.
Why do you say damn?
Why are you all writing minus two?
Is that not how you say it?
Oh, you guys are also telling me what your guys' prescription is?
It's a Twitch joke?
Okay, yeah.
I'm not in on all these Twitch jokes.
I am in on the 6.7 though.
Stay mad.
Dude, every time I see my cat, I go 6.7 and I make a...
No, I'm kidding.
I'm not doing that.
Ah, I couldn't even do it.
Ah, no, Aki.
I would rather not, actually.
Sometimes you stumble on these things and it just happens.
It means good or bad joke, plus two or minus two.
Oh, okay.
But why are you writing minus two?
That was...
Oh!
Because I said minus two.
Of course.
Alright.
I guess me having a prescription of minus two isn't funny.
Wow, you have a big discrepancy between your two eyes, Ibialo.
Isn't that a big discrepancy?
But I guess you see just fine with that, right?
Are you actually at minus ten and minus eight?
You must have really thick glasses then.
Do they weigh a lot?
Wow, okay.
Damn.
Now I'm not feeling like my eyesight is that bad.
They know glass magic?
It's not that thick?
Okay.
I wonder if you have a minus two, does that simply mean your eyesight is like 18 and not 20-20?
But what about plus two then?
Maybe that's the same.
You go down two as well.
I don't know.
On that scale.
You know when you say you have 20-20 vision?
If you have a minus two, what does that take you on that scale, you know?
Yeah, I guess it's gotta be some kind of material that has a bigger refractory...
What is the English name for that?
The index of bending light, right?
Snell's Law.
Did you make him pretty thin?
Okay, okay.
Refraction index, yeah.
That's the one.
Oh, no.
Plastic!
I don't think that's used, is it?
Unless...
Really?
No way.
It's glasses.
Plexiglass.
Maybe.
Guys, what should I play next?
I'm thinking of the Iron Long game, because it's kinda short.
On stream.
But like, what other game could be cool?
I mean, I'm gonna take a look at my backlog, of course, but...
What are you feeling like these days?
What genre?
Probably not puzzle.
Because I've played so many puzzle games lately, and my brain is breaking from it.
The Looker?
That sounds like a puzzle game, is it?
You guys are loving puzzle games.
Even though I'm not that great at puzzle games.
You guys are just like...
Puzzle game!
We wanna watch puzzle games.
Pacific Drive!
Oh, that's a good one, I guess.
It's not too long either, right?
It's slight horror, as I understand it.
But that's fine with me, you know?
Just like...
Spooky vibes.
Not straight up Amnesia style, because that game...
Kills me, man.
As you'll find out later today.
Holy shit.
That is...
Honestly, at this point, it may be the...
Nah, okay, it's really early still, but man.
Man, I've already played The Witness.
I got pretty far.
I got stuck on one puzzle at some point, and then I just sort of...
got out of it, I didn't play it for a bit, and then I quit.
I was almost done with the game.
I wouldn't say The Witness was super difficult, except that one puzzle that just broke me.
I couldn't do it.
So, except for that one puzzle, I did pretty well, I think.
Any Switch platformer would be cool.
Oh, yeah.
Or maybe I'll do a Nintendo game on stream.
Ocarina of Time?
Yeah, maybe.
I have no plans for Silksong, meaning I don't know when I'll play it, but I will play it.
The Looker is different than The Witness.
It's a game appreciating and making fun of it.
What?
Making...
Why would you make fun of it?
It's a...
The Witness is a great game.
What?
It is overwhelmingly positive.
Damn.
Okay.
Really?
Okay, well in that case, maybe I'll try The Looker.
Is it difficult?
It's a homage and a parody.
Okay.
Interesting.
It's very short.
Okay, okay, okay.
Cool.
Yeah, maybe we'll do a stream where I play like The Looker, Iron Long, you know, all these really short games.
I also wanna have a stream where I play shitty games.
Or not like shitty games, but...
Let's just say really unknown games, because it could be fun.
Back to the stranger I go?
Bye-bye.
Have fun in the stranger.
I have played Inside Astro.
It's on my channel.
It's an incredible game.
Really love that one.
Man, maybe I could play the other game by...
Playdead.
Limbo.
I haven't played that.
Maybe that's an idea.
That's also relatively short, right?
Limbo, yeah.
It's a classic.
Okay.
Well, guys, thank you for your inputs.
I will think about it.
But now I'm gonna go.
Thanks for watching, and thanks for subscribing.
And hanging out, chatting with me, and just...
Making fun of me and stuff.
It's actually pretty cool.
I'll see you next time, okay?
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.